<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Praiamar</string>




    <!--Litoral Norte-->

    <string name="north_coast_name">North Coast</string>
    <string name="north_coast_preview">North coast full of charms…</string>


    <string name="calhetas_beach_name">Calhetas Beach</string>
    <string name="calhetas_beach_preview">This is one of the most beautiful beaches in Brazil. The beach…</string>
    <string name="calhetas_beach_description">This is one of the most beautiful beaches in Brazil. Praia de Calhetas, located in the municipality of Santo Agostinho, is always full of tourists. In the region, get ready to find crystal clear and calm waters, vegetation and sports options. In addition to a calm sea, which favors diving, in the region you can still make trails, zip lines, or just enjoy the scenery.</string>

    <string name="boa_viagem_beach_name">Boa Viagem Beach</string>
    <string name="boa_viagem_beach_preview">Among the tourist beaches of Pernambuco, this is one...</string>
    <string name="boa_viagem_beach_description">Among the tourist beaches of Pernambuco, this is one of the most popular in Recife. With many coconut trees around, Praia dde Boa Viagem has a long stretch of sand and a greenish sea. The good news is that there are many kiosks and tents on the edge, which sell tasty portions and drinks. Be sure to take a swim in the sea, as the waters are calm and with pleasant temperatures.</string>

    <string name="forte_orange_beach_name">Forte Orange Beach</string>
    <string name="forte_orange_beach_preview">Located on the island of Itamaracá, Praia do Forte Orange...</string>
    <string name="forte_orange_beach_description">Located on the island of Itamaracá, Praia do Forte Orange is perfect for those who want to enjoy a lively and relaxed atmosphere. In addition to being the owner of beautiful tropical landscapes, it offers water sports, such as diving and stand-up paddle. The calm and pleasant waters make bathing in the sea even more delicious.</string>

    <string name="janga_beach_name">Janga Beach</string>
    <string name="janga_beach_preview">Janga Beach is located in the most urban area...</string>
    <string name="janga_beach_description">Janga Beach is located in the most urban area of Recife. On site you will find an extensive stretch of sand, perfect for walking. The sea is calm and the waters are transparent, which makes for a delicious swim. It is possible to practice water sports such as kayaking and jet skiing. The region is not very busy, ensuring moments of greater tranquility.</string>


    <!--Litoral Sul-->

    <string name="south_coast_name">"South Coast</string>
    <string name="south_coast_preview">When choosing the beaches of Pernambuco, south coast…</string>

    <string name="porto_de_galinhas_beach_name">Porto de Galinhas Beach</string>
    <string name="porto_de_galinhas_beach_preview">When choosing the beaches of Pernambuco, south coast...</string>
    <string name="porto_de_galinhas_beach_description">When choosing the beaches of Pernambuco, south coast, of course, Porto de Galinhas cannot be missing from your itinerary. In this region, the beaches are beautiful and surrounded by coconut trees, blue sea and transparent waters. The beach that bears the districts name owns the most incredible scenery in the southern region. Dont miss diving to observe fish of different species and coral reefs!"</string>

    <string name="maracaipe_beach_name">Maracaipe Beach</string>
    <string name="maracaipe_beach_preview">You will be enchanted by Maracaipe Beach. Far away...</string>
    <string name="maracaipe_beach_description">You will be enchanted by Maracaipe Beach. Far from the urban area, the region guarantees the most beautiful landscapes in Pernambuco. The beach has a wide stretch of soft white sand, perfect for those who like to take a walk and admire the scenery. In this region, the sea is rough and attracts many surfers.</string>

    <string name="muro_alto_beach_name">Muro Alto Beach</string>
    <string name="muro_alto_beach_preview">Also in the Porto de Galinhas district, Praia de Muro...</string>
    <string name="muro_alto_beach_description">Also in the district of Porto de Galinhas, Praia de Muro Alto has 3-metre cliffs, which form beautiful walls along its entire edge. The reefs are also highlights in the landscape, and form natural pools with calm and warm waters. On a stretch of beach, it is possible to ride a jet ski. To enjoy the entire region, rent a buggy and also take a ride on the soft white sands.</string>

    <string name="carneiros_beach_name">Carneiros Beach</string>
    <string name="carneiros_beach_preview">Located in the city of Tamandaré, Carneiros is one of the beaches...</string>
    <string name="carneiros_beach_description">Located in the city of Tamandaré, Carneiros is one of the most beautiful beaches in the state. Surrounded by coconut trees and with a sea of ​​crystal clear water, it is still very charming and historic. Be sure to enjoy the beach, but take the opportunity to visit the church of São Benedito, dating from the 18th century - which is the stage for weddings, including famous ones. It is one of the most popular honeymoon beaches in Pernambuco.</string>

    <!--Piscinas Naturais-->

    <string name="natural_pools_name">"Natural Pools</string>
    <string name="natural_pools_preview">This is a Brazilian unanimity, when thinking about a natural pool…</string>

    <string name="porto_de_galinhas_natural_pools_name">Porto de Galinhas Natural Pool</string>
    <string name="porto_de_galinhas_natural_pools_preview">This is a Brazilian unanimity, when thinking about swimming pool..</string>
    <string name="porto_de_galinhas_natural_pools_description">This is a Brazilian unanimity, when you think about a natural pool, the beach at Porto de Galinhas comes to mind. Porto de Galinhas beach is located in the Municipality of Ipojuca and approximately 49.2 Km from Recife International Airport. In about 1 hour leaving the capital, you arrive at these, which are one of the 7 wonders of Pernambuco, the natural pools of Porto de Galinhas.</string>

    <string name="muro_alto_natural_pools_name">Muro Alto Natural Pool</string>
    <string name="muro_alto_natural_pools_preview">From the side of Porto de Galinhas, there is the beach of Muro Alto with its ...</string>
    <string name="muro_alto_natural_pools_description">On the side of Porto de Galinhas, there is Muro Alto beach with its “giant” pool. The beach has a wall of corals that reach 3km in length and therefore forms a large pool. At low tide the view is amazing, you can go swimming to the coral wall or using a kayak/stand up paddle. You can also take a raft ride or just enjoy the calm and crystalline sea of ​​this beach.</string>

    <string name="carneiros_beach_natural_pools_name">Carneiros Beach Natural Pool</string>
    <string name="carneiros_beach_natural_pools_preview">Praia dos Carneiros is located in the municipality of Tamandaré, 113 Km away...</string>
    <string name="carneiros_beach_natural_pools_description">Praia dos Carneiros is located in the municipality of Tamandaré, 113 km from Recife. This beach was elected the second best beach in Brazil, according to the TripAdvisor websites O Travellers Choice 2017 award. There you will find sandbanks, natural pools, corals, a medicinal clay bath, mangroves and everything with a good infrastructure. structure for you to enjoy your day. You can explore the beach by walking, boating, kayaking, stand up paddle and much more.</string>


    <!--Ilhas -->

    <string name="islands_name">"Islands</string>
    <string name="islands_preview">North coast full of charms…</string>


    <!--Parques Aquáticos -->

    <string name="water_parks_name">"Water Parks</string>
    <string name="water_parks_preview">Located on the north coast of Pernambuco it is synonymous with…</string>


    <!--Sobre Praiamar-->

    <string name="about_praiamar_name">"About Praiamar</string>
    <string name="about_praiamar_preview">Don\'t just stay here. See also…</string>
</resources>